<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on @magcamit</title>
    <link>https://www.magcamit.com/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on @magcamit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; {year}, Michael Intal Magcamit</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.magcamit.com/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SeReNa-SEA</title>
      <link>https://www.magcamit.com/project/serena-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.magcamit.com/project/serena-sea/</guid>
      <description>The Divine Tragedy of Securing the Sacred: Security, Religion, and Nationalism in Southeast Asia
A EU Horizon 2020 Marie Skłodowska-Curie Project: 1 Mar 2019 &amp;ndash; 28 Feb 2021. See the SeReNa-SEA project factsheet.
 Fieldworks Public Engagements A Case For Godless States (monograph) Why Nation-States Persist (journal manuscript) The Divine Tragedy of Securing the Sacred (journal manuscript)  In the quest to understand In 2017, I travelled to Southeast Asia to visit and survey the locales where I will be conducting my Marie Curie research on the three-way nexus between security, religion, and nationalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SecTraLink-EA</title>
      <link>https://www.magcamit.com/project/sectralink-ea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.magcamit.com/project/sectralink-ea/</guid>
      <description>Small Powers and Trading Security: Contexts, Motives, and Outcomes is available for purchase on the following websites.
 https://bit.ly/2HGnOq9 https://bit.ly/2JryDyM https://bit.ly/2JDZdFh https://bit.ly/2YbbRie https://amzn.to/2CtnAiV https://bit.ly/2Wb3gtM https://bit.ly/2CsXJr3  About the book This book examines why and how small powers link their security interests and trade agendas, and how security threats influence the facilitation and outcome of their trade activities. In doing so, it analyses the increasingly complex connections between trade and security, demonstrating how these linkages affect the overall security of four small but important states in East Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>